{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ht","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"gov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"zin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ovd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"deći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
